https://www.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/terms-conditions/

Skip to contentTerms & ConditionsEffective Date: March 31, 2020Hackensack Meridian Health
Website Terms of UseThank you for visiting Hackensack Meridian Health’s website.PLEASE REVIEW THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE Hackensack Meridian Health (“Hackensack Meridian Health”, “HMH”, “We” or “Our”) WEBSITE, INCLUDING ANY OF OUR DIGITIAL CONTENT OR ONLINE SERVICES OR FEATURES AVAILABLE ON OUR WEBSITE (the “Site”). BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU ARE ENTERING INTO A LEGAL AGREEMENT WITH Hackensack Meridian Health REGARDING YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY PORTION OF THESE TERMS OF USE, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.1. Not Medical Advice. The information provided on the Site is for educational purposes only and is designed to support, not replace, the relationship that exists between patient/site visitor and his/her physician. The information on this Site is not intended to constitute medical advice or replace the medical advice of your doctor or healthcare provider. Please consult your healthcare provider for advice about a specific medical condition.2. Compliance with Law. You agree that you will not violate any local, state, federal or international laws in using or accessing this Site.3. Site Use and Content. You may view, download, copy or print a single copy of any page from our Site for personal, non-commercial purposes, provided you do not remove, modify, or alter any copyright or proprietary rights notices that may appear on the Site. You may not otherwise use, modify, copy, translate, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, print, display, distribute, publish or sell any portion of our Site without our express prior written consent. You may not use any portion of this Site, including any materials, documents, images, graphics, logos, designs, audio, video or any other information on the Site (the “Content”) for any commercial purpose. In using our Site, you additionally agree (a) not to create a browser or border environment, or graphical user interface around the Site; (b) not to interfere with or disrupt the operation of the Site, or the servers or networks that host the Site or make the materials available, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies, or regulations of such servers or networks; (c) not to interfere with or violate other Site users’ right to privacy or other rights, or harvest or collect personally identifiable information about users without their express consent, including using any robot, spider, crawler, site search or retrieval application, or other manual or automatic device or process to retrieve, index and/or data-mine information; (d) not to impersonate any person or entity or provide false personal information or business information, for the purpose of receiving the materials provided on this Site or gaining unlawful access to it; (e) not to falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with any person or entity, including without limitation, with Hackensack Meridian Health, or express or imply that Hackensack Meridian Health endorses or is in any way affiliated with you or any statement you make, or present any false information about this Site; (f) not to transmit or otherwise make available in connection with the materials or content on this Site, any virus, “worm”, “Trojan horse”, “time bomb”, “web bug”, spyware, or any other computer code, file, or program that is malicious by nature or defective, and may, or is intended to damage or hijack the operation of any hardware, software, or telecommunications equipment, or any other actually or potentially harmful, disruptive, or invasive code or component; (g) not to transmit any communications or content of any type that may infringe or violate any right of any party, or otherwise use this Site for any illegal or unauthorized purpose; and (h) not to share, post or publish any content through or on this Site which may be reasonably interpreted as disturbing, objectionable, obscene, abusive or offensive to others.4. Your Site Access. Hackensack Meridian Health reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to prohibit, restrict or discontinue your access to certain pages within the Site if you violate any of these Terms of Use, as Hackensack Meridian Health may determine in its sole discretion.5. MEDICAL DISCLAIMER. IF THIS IS A MEDICAL EMERGENCY, PLEASE IMMEDIATELY CALL EMERGENCY PERSONNEL (911) TO GET PROMPT MEDICAL ATTENTION. DO NOT RELY ON ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS THROUGH THIS SITE FOR ASSISTANCE IN REGARD TO YOUR MEDICAL NEEDS, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY IMMEDIATE, URGENT MEDICAL NEEDS.6. Security. All forms that request personal information (name, address, email address, etc.) are secure and provide encrypted transmission over the Internet. Please refer to our Website Privacy Policy for more information concerning encryption technology utilized by Hackensack Meridian Health. We protect personal information that is otherwise collected or transmitted through this Site by using commercially reasonable security measures to prevent against loss, misuse or unauthorized access to such information. Please note, however, that there are inherent risks in transmitting information over the Internet, and Hackensack Meridian Health cannot guarantee that unauthorized access to or use of your personal information will never occur.7. DISCLAIMERS. MATERIALS, SERVICES AND OTHER INFORMATION ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BY Hackensack Meridian Health AND Hackensack Meridian Health MAKES NO EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR USE, TITLE OR NON INFRINGEMENT. ALTHOUGH OUR HEALTH INFORMATION CONTENT IS REVIEWED AND APPROVED BY HEALTHCARE PROFESSIONALS, Hackensack Meridian Health DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, OR COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS OR FOR THE RESULTS OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF SUCH INFORMATION. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT Hackensack Meridian Health DOES NOT OPERATE OR CONTROL THE INTERNET AND THEREFORE Hackensack Meridian Health DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT THE USE OF THIS SITE WILL BE ERROR FREE OR FREE OF TECHNOLOGY DOWNTIMES OR UNAVAILABILITY. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT Hackensack Meridian Health CANNOT AND DOES NOT GUARANTEE AGAINST VIRUSES, WORMS, OR OTHER UNAUTHORIZED USERS OR HACKERS ATTEMPTING TO OBTAIN ACCESS TO THIS SITE OR INFORMATION TRANSMITTED TO OR FROM THIS SITE.8. Discontinuance of Site. Hackensack Meridian Health reserves the right to temporarily or permanently discontinue this Site or any page, functionality, feature or portion of this Site, at any time and without notice.9. Intellectual Property. All trademarks, service marks, and logos and copyrights displayed and used in this Site are the property of Hackensack Meridian Health or their respective owners. Nothing on this Site may be construed as granting you any right or license to use any trademark or other intellectual property right without the written permission of its owner. The selection, arrangement, compilation and presentation of all information and materials on our Site are the exclusive property of Hackensack Meridian Health. You may not reproduce in any form or by any means (except as provided in Section 3 (“Site Use and Content”)) any information, materials or Content on our Site without Hackensack Meridian Health’s express written authorization. Neither the name of Hackensack Meridian Health, nor any of Hackensack Meridian Health’s trademarks, service marks or copyrighted material may be used in any way, including in any advertising, hyperlink, publicity or promotional materials, without Hackensack Meridian Health’s express written permission.10. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. IN NO EVENT SHALL Hackensack Meridian Health BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER MONETARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING FEES OR PENALTIES IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THIS SITE OR MATERIALS POSTED ON THIS SITE OR CONNECTIVITY TO OR FROM THIS SITE TO ANY OTHER SITE. SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILIITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES; IN SUCH STATES OR JURISDICTIONS, OUR LIABLITY WILL BE LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW.11. Governing Law and Jurisdiction. You agree that any claim or dispute relating to the Hackensack Meridian Health Site or your use or reliance on this Site shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New Jersey without regard to its conflict of laws provisions. The parties agree to be bound and shall submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the local, state or federal courts located in Middlesex County, New Jersey.12. Username and Password. In the event you access any service on this Site requiring a username and password, you are solely responsible for keeping such username and password strictly confidential.13. Inbound Links. You may not, under any circumstances, establish a link to the Hackensack Meridian Health website without the express written consent of the General Counsel of Hackensack Meridian Health, including but not limited to deep linking.14. External Links. Please note that pages of this Site may be linked to other sites which may have different terms of use. Hackensack Meridian Health does not own, control, manage, supervise, direct or otherwise have any involvement in the business or affairs of any third party site. Hackensack Meridian Health is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any third party site. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy and terms of that site. Hackensack Meridian Health encourages you to be aware when you are leaving Hackensack Meridian Health’s Site to read the privacy statements and terms of each and every website that you visit before providing any personally identifiable information.15. Your Representations and Warranties. As a condition of your use of our Site, you hereby represent and warrant that: (a) you possess the legal authority to enter into these Terms of Use and to form a binding agreement under applicable law; (b) you will use our Site in accordance with these Terms of Use and fully perform your obligations hereunder; and (c) your agreement to these Terms of Use does not and will not violate any other agreement to which you are subject.16. Modification of Terms of Use. Hackensack Meridian Health may modify these Terms of Use at any time without prior notice. The modified Terms of Use will be effective upon posting on our Site and the new effective date will be indicated in the modified Terms of Use. To remain aware of the current terms, Hackensack Meridian Health suggests that you review the Terms of Use, as well as the other website policies listed above, at regular intervals.17. Ways in which HMH May Use Certain Personal Information About You.  You agree that, should you elect to provide it, HMH Care may use personally identifiable information (PII) you provide, which may include your name, e-mail address, physical address, or other data to communicate with you. HMH may use this information as necessary to enforce these Terms of Use. You may request to have this information modified or deleted from our records. To make any such requests, please contact HMH.18. Non-Personally Identifiable Information.  When you visit HMH’s Site, we automatically collect and store non-personally identifiable information such as data sent by your web browser.  We also collect standard information about your computer, such as your web browser and operating system, and about your usage of our Site, such as pages visited, length of visit, and search queries. This information, which does not identify you personally, is aggregated and used to help diagnose problems and suggest areas for improving our Site.19. Cookies.  Like many websites, some portions of our Site use cookies.  Cookies are text files that may be transferred to your computer or mobile device through your web browsing software. These cookies are used to remember your preferences or to track statistics on usage of various portions of HMH websites.You can choose not to accept cookies by selecting settings on your web browser that block or restrict the use of cookies. You can also delete cookies that have been placed on your computer or device. Please be advised that if you block or restrict the use of cookies, you may not be able to use certain functions or features on our Site.20. Sharing Your Information.  HMH may share your PII only as is permitted under institutional policies and in compliance with applicable federal and state laws and regulations. Specifically, HMH may share your PII: (a) with authorized third party service providers as needed to manage the operation of our Site; (b) as needed to comply with applicable law, regulation, legal process, subpoena or government request; (c) as needed to enforce these Terms of Use, including to carry out an investigation of potential violations of the Terms of Use; (d) as needed to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues relating to our Site; (e) to respond to claims that any content available on our Site violates the rights of any third party; (f) in connection with any change in control, including by way of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of HMH’s assets; (g) as needed to protect the rights, property, or safety of other Site users or the general public; or (h) pursuant to your express prior consent.21. Behavioral Advertising.  HMH may contract with third-party vendors to show our advertisements on non-HMH websites and digital properties. HMH and third-party vendors with whom we contract may use cookies and web beacons to serve our ads based on your prior visit or visits to HMH websites and to assess the effectiveness of our ads. This is also called “targeted advertising” or “interest-based advertising.” These techniques use only non-personally identifiable information.22. Protected Health Information. Please read the full text of our Notice of Privacy Practices to understand how any Protected Health Information (“PHI”), as that term is defined in the Notice of Privacy Practices (HIPAA), that you submit via our Site will be treated.23. Children. Except as otherwise indicated, Hackensack Meridian Health does not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 18. The content of our Site is directed at adults, and therefore this Site is intended for use only by adults over the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please consult a parent or guardian for help in using this Site.24. Questions about these Terms of Use. If you have any questions or comments regarding these Terms of Use, please contact Hackensack Meridian Health.  We will attempt to respond in a timely manner.
Array
(
)Share This Page
